Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS.180
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Haunted Houses (1987), 194157
  - Series V, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution, 194158
    - Reviews (Robert Gluck), Undated; 194160 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Second Shift - "Like Mother, Like Daughter" extract, 1993; 194159 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Series VI: Motion Sickness (1991), 194134
  Series VI: Motion Sickness contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Motion Sickness". This series includes annotated drafts of the book and mentions, publicity, and reviews in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series VI, Subseries A: Drafts and Production, 194144
    - Annotated chapters 1-7, Undated; 194156 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Annotated chapters 7-12, Undated; 194155 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Annotated chapters 13-end, Undated; 194154 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Annotated page proofs (1 of 2), Undated; 194153 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Annotated page proofs (2 of 2), Undated; 194152 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Excerpt from "Homesick" - annotated original, Undated; 194151 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - HSK / Australians / etc..., Undated; 194150 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (1 of 4), Undated; 194149 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (2 of 4), Undated; 194148 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (3 of 4), Undated; 194147 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (4 of 4), Undated; 194146 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Uncorrected Proof, Undated; 194145 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Series VI, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution, 194135
    - Motion Sickness and Absence Makes the Heart Review, 1991; 194143 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Press, 1991; 194142 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Press and Publicity, 1991-1993; 194141 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Press and Publicity, Undated; 194140 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Required Reading - for Postmodernism and comtemporary culture with Prof. Thomas Keenan, 1995; 194139 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Review, 1991; 194138 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Review, 1993; 194137 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Review - German Press, 1995; 194136 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Series VII: Cast in Doubt (1992), 194079
  Series VII: Cast in Doubt contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Cast in Doubt". This series includes annotated drafts of the book, cover art, the press release, and publicity and reviews in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series VII, Subseries A: Drafts and Production, 194093
    - Annotated original manuscript (1 of 2), Undated; 194133 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Annotated original manuscript (2 of 2), Undated; 194132 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Articles: Politics and Art, 1992; 194131 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Bob Siegle internet conversation, Undated; 194130 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Cast in Doubt - Advance uncorrected proof, Undated; 194129 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Chapters 1-5, annotated, Undated; 194128 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Chapters 1-5 (1 of 2), Undated; 194127 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Chapters 6-11, annotated, Undated; 194126 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Chapters 6-12 (2 of 2), Undated; 194125 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Chapters 12-end, annotated, Undated; 194124 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Chapter 16 - Helen's Diary, Undated; 194123 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Chapter 17 #6 - Coda, the Rough Future, Undated; 194122 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Chapter 17 #7 - Coda, the Rough Future, Undated; 194121 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Chapter 17 #7 - Coda - The Rough Future, Undated; 194120 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Coda, Undated; 194119 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Color Copy of Artwork for cover, Undated; 194118 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Copies and Page proofs with annotations, Undated; 194117 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Copy Edited and Final Version chapters 1-6 (1 of 3), Undated; 194116 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Copy Edited and Final Version chapters 7-13 (2 of 3), Undated; 194115 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Copy Edited and Final Version chapters 14-end and notes (3 of 3), Undated; 194114 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Cover Negative, Undated; 194113 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Cover Proof with corrections, Undated; 194112 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Draft - chapters 1-5 annotated, Undated; 194111 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Draft - chapters 6-12, Undated; 194110 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Draft - chapters 13-coda, Undated; 194109 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Draft I - Fonda's corrections chapters 1-6, Undated; 194108 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Draft I - Fonda's corrections chapters 7-12, Undated; 194107 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Draft I - Fonda's corrections chapters 13-coda, Undated; 194106 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Draft III - chapters 1-6, Undated; 194105 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Draft III - chapters 7-13, Undated; 194104 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Draft III - chapters 14-Coda, Undated; 194103 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Draft folder - labeled Crete, Undated; 194102 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Helen's Diary - chapter 16 #6, Undated; 194101 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Memorandum of Agreements, 1993; 194100 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Microfilm copies - activities in New York Theater, 1941; 194099 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Notes, annotated work copy, edits, Undated; 194098 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Notes, newsclippings, D. Dean letter, Undated; 194097 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Paperback cover with note from Fonda Duvanel, Undated; 194096 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Publisher letter, Undated; 194095 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Timeline, Undated; 194094 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Series VII, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution, 194080
    - Press and Publicity, Undated; 194092 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, Undated; 194091 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Promotional agenda, Undated; 194090 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Publicity, Undated; 194089 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Publicity, 1992; 194088 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Reviews, 1994-1995; 194087 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Reviews, 1992-1995; 194086 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, 1992; 194085 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Reviews, Undated; 194084 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Reviews, Undated; 194083 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Serpent's Tail Promotion folder, Undated; 194082 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Tour - Mind King program, resume, Undated; 194081 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Series VIII: The Velvet Years (1995), 194030
  Series VIII: The Velvet Years contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "The Velvet Years". This series includes research for the book, writing fragments, interviews collected by Lynne Tillman, and publicity through magazines and newspapers. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series VIII, Subseries A: Drafts and Production, 194060
    - American Center - Warhol Film and Television; War Without Enemies, 1994; 194078 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Callie Angel's Warhol exhibition, Undated; 194077 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Contemporary newspaper articles - research, 1993-1994; 194076 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Copies of pictures - not needed (1 of 2), Undated; 194075 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Copies of pictures - not needed (2 of 2), Undated; 194074 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Letters and correspondence - research, 1994; 194073 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Map and captions; editing comments, 1994; 194072 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Notes and fragments, Undated; 194071 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Pavillion, 1994-1995; 194070 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Photocopied pages from "The Autobiography and Sex Life of Andy Warhol", Undated; 194069 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Raw material - Warhol, the Velvets, and the Factory (Annotated), 1994; 194068 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Reflections on Andy Warhol (various people), Undated; 194067 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Research materials for "The Velvet Years", Undated; 194066 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Research - newspaper articles and notes, Undated; 194065 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Warhol Box by David Dalton, Undated; 194064 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Warhol Files - notes, contacts, notecards, letters, and transcript fragments, Undated; 194063 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Whitney Museum - "The Films of Andy Warhol, Part II", Undated; 194062 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Writing fragments, annotated, Undated; 194061 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Series VIII, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution, 194031
    - Book Receipt, 1998; 194059 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Billy Name, Undated; 194058 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Danny Fields, Undated; 194057 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Donald Lyons, Undated; 194056 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Gerard Malanga, Undated; 194055 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Gordon Baldwin, Undated; 194054 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews John Ashberry, Undated; 194053 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews John Cale, 1993; 194052 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Jonas Mekas, Undated; 194051 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Mary Woronov, Undated; 194050 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Maureen Tucker, Undated; 194049 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Pat Hatley, Undated; 194048 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Paul Morrisey, Undated; 194047 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Sam Green, Undated; 194046 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Stephen Shore, Undated; 194045 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Stephen Shore, Undated; 194044 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Sterling Morrison, Undated; 194043 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Susan Bottomly, Undated; 194042 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Taylor Mead, Undated; 194041 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Mentions, 1995-1996; 194040 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Press and Publicity, 1996; 194039 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Press and Publicity, 1996; 194038 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Promotional Photographs, Undated; 194037 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Review, 1997; 194036 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Reviews, 1996; 194035 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Reviews and Mentions, 1995; 194034 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Transcript of Tillman interview with Henry Geldzanler, Undated; 194033 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Transcript of Tillman interviews with Ultra Violet, Undated; 194032 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Series IX: No Lease on Life (1997), 193976
  Series IX: No Lease on Life contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "No Lease on Life". This series includes annotated and edited drafts of the book, and reviews and publicity in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series IX, Subseries A: Drafts and Production, 193995
    - Annotated uncorrected proof, Undated; 194029 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Draft, Undated; 194028 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Draft, Undated; 194027 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Draft - labeled pages 1-5, Undated; 194026 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 194025 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 194024 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 194023 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 194022 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 194021 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 194020 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 194019 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 194018 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Draft "Elizabeth 6A pages 49-62", Undated; 194017 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Draft "From Elizabeth 6A", Undated; 194016 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Draft fragment, Undated; 194015 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Draft fragments, planning, Manhattan transit, Undated; 194014 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Draft and Notes, Undated; 194013 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Edited Copy from Publisher (1 of 2), Undated; 194012 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Edited Copy from Publisher (2 of 2), Undated; 194011 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Elizabeth draft, Undated; 194010 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Elizabeth - newspaper clippings, Undated; 194009 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Form for Jacket Flaps and Verso, Undated; 194008 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Frank's notes, Undated; 194007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Matchbook jacket with text, Undated; 194006 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - "Next to Nothing" for Laconian Inc., 1996; 194005 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Undated; 194004 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Original Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 194003 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Original Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 194002 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Part 1 of 2 (Draft), Undated; 194001 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Part 2 of 2 (Draft), Undated; 194000 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - "Reckless Disregard", Undated; 193999 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Short - "For Aperture", Undated; 193998 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Uncorrected Book Proof, 1998; 193997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Uncorrected Book Proof, Undated; 193996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Series IX, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution, 193977
    - "Die Mieteren" - German Press, 1998; 193994 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - English publicity and press, 1998-2000; 193993 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - German Press, 1998; 193992 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Manhattan Bus map, 1996; 193991 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - New York - events, publicity, 1998; 193990 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - No Lease on Life and Bookstore, 2000; 193989 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - On the writing of "No Lease on Life", Undated; 193988 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Paperback publication announcement, Undated; 193987 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Press, 1998-1999; 193986 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Press, Undated; 193985 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Press, Undated; 193984 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Promotional Tour (Portland, Seattle, Oakland, Los Angeles, 1997; 193983 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Publicity, Undated; 193982 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Publicity, Undated; 193981 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Publicity contacts and Bio materials, Undated; 193980 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Reviews, 1996-1998; 193979 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1997-2005; 193978 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Series X: Bookstore (1999), 193941
  Series X: Bookstore contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Bookstore". This series includes research, annotated drafts of the book, and press and reviews in newspapers and magazines, including the Books & Co. "Off the Wall" newsletter. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series X, Subseries A: Drafts and Production, 193951
    - Annotated Uncorrected Proof, 1999; 193975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Books & Co. Editing Notes, 1999; 193974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Books & Co. Farewell Mailing, 1997; 193973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Books & Co. - Lynne Tillman Research and News Stories, 1997-1998; 193972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Books & Co. - Rebecca's Research, 1998; 193971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Covers, Captions, and Images, Undated; 193970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Draft Comments, 1997; 193969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Edited Manuscript pages 1-118 (1 of 2), 1998; 193968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Edited Manuscript pages 119-237 (2 of 2), 1998; 193967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Edits and Changes; Permissions and Comment Drafts, 1998-1999; 193966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - First Draft with J. Watson's Annotations (1 of 2), 1998; 193965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - First Draft with J. Watson's Annotations (2 of 2), 1998; 193964 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Harcourt Brace and Co. Dust Jacket, 1999; 193963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Index Draft, Undated; 193962 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Interview Releases and Consent Forms for "Bookstore: The Life and Times of Jeannette Watson and Books & Co., 1998; 193961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Jeannette Watson Sanger's Resume, Undated; 193960 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript (1 of 2), 1998; 193959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript (2 of 2), 1998; 193958 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Page Proofs (1 of 2), 1999; 193957 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Page Proofs (2 of 2), 1999; 193956 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Paragraphs, Undated; 193955 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Pen Panel on Specialty Bookstores; Lynne Tillman remarks and Flier, 1998; 193954 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Research about Bookstores, 1981-1998; 193953 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Transcription Invoices, Checks, Receipts, 1997; 193952 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Series X, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution, 193942
    - Books & Co. "Off the Wall" newsletter, 1997; 193950 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Bookstore Contacts, Reviews, Features, Promotional Events, 1998-1999; 193949 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Panel, 1999; 193948 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Press, Publicity, and Events, 1999; 193947 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Publicity, Undated; 193946 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Publicity Package, Undated; 193945 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, 1999-2000; 193944 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1999; 193943 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Series XI: American Genius (2006), 193879
  Series XI: American Genius contains materials related to the creation of Lynne Tillman's book "American Genius". This series includes various annotated drafts of the book, however there is no press or publicity in this series. The series is divided into one subseries:
  - Series XI, Subseries A: Drafts and Production, 193880
    - American Genius Annotated Draft (2 of 3), Undated; 193940 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Part 1 is in: Box 22, Folder 13 Part 3 is in: Box 22, Folder 27
    - American Genius Annotated Draft fragment - pages 13-165 and 62-95, Undated; 193939 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Gray" pages 1-115 (1 of 3), Undated; 193938 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Gray" pages 116-242 (2 of 3), Undated; 193937 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Gray" pages 243-357 (3 of 3), Undated; 193936 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft fragment pages 27-40, Undated; 193935 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft fragment pages 69-103, Undated; 193934 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes (1 of 4), Undated; 193933 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes pages 1-142 (2 of 4), Undated; 193932 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes pages 143-293 (3 of 4), Undated; 193931 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes pages 294-377 (4 of 4), Undated; 193930 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 108-213, Undated; 193929 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 147-183, Undated; 193928 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 372-393, Undated; 193927 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 385-409 and unnumbered, Undated; 193926 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 420-425 with three iterations, Undated; 193925 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 430-434, with E-Mail from Lynne Tillman to Steve, 2004; 193924 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, several annotated copies pages 1, 424, notes and fragments, Undated; 193923 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Steve's" (1 of 3), Undated; 193922 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Steve's" (2 of 3), Undated; 193921 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Steve's" (3 of 3), Undated; 193920 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - American Genius Draft "End Desktop", Undated; 193919 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - American Genius Draft Pages 2-91, 32-33, Undated; 193918 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - American Genius "From December 17th Draft", 2001; 193917 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - American Genius Full Draft pages 1-123 (1 of 3), Undated; 193916 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - American Genius Full Draft pages 124-284 (2 of 3), Undated; 193915 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - American Genius Full Draft pages 285-423 (3 of 3), Undated; 193914 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - American Genius "Last Pages as of 9/11/04, 11 Sept. 2004; 193913 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - American Genius "Last Pages", 19 Sept. 2004; 193912 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - American Genius Notes and Annotated Draft (1 of 3), Undated; 193911 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - American Genius Notes and Annotated Draft (2 of 3), Undated; 193910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - American Genius Notes and Annotated Draft (3 of 3), Undated; 193909 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - American Genius Research File, Skin, 2002-2003; 193908 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American Genius SIngle Spaced Draft pages 41-120, Undated; 193907 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - American Skin #28 Annotated Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 193906 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - American Skin #28 Annotated Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 193905 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - American Skin #29 Annotated Draft 9 Dec. 2003 (1 of 2), 193904 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American Skin #29 Annotated Draft 9 Dec. 2003 (2 of 2), 193903 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - American Skin #33 Annotated Draft (1 of 2), Undated; 193902 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - American Skin #33 Annotated Draft (2 of 2), Undated; 193901 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - American Skin Annotated Draft dated Dec. 14, 2002, 193900 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - American Skin "Done in Germany" pages 349-409, Undated; 193899 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - American Skin "Skin 27" (1 of 3), 2002; 193898 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Part 2 is in: Box 21, Folder 1 Part 3 is in: Box 22, Folder 27
    - "Costume Ball" Sketches and Noted toward American Genius and the Undiagnosed, Undated; 193897 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Instead, May 29, 2001; 193896 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Instead, Undated; 193895 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Instead, Undated; 193894 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Instead, Undated; 193893 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Instead, Undated; 193892 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Instead, Undated; 193891 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Instead - Annotated, June 18, 2001; 193890 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Instead - Annotated, Undated; 193889 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Instead of Nothing - Annotated Draft, Undated; 193888 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Instead "Read This 2/13/01 Art in General", Feb. 13, 2001; 193887 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Kingsley Hall Draft, Undated; 193886 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Seance Revisions, Nov. 2004; 193885 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Skin 18 (3 of 3), Undated; 193884 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      Part 1 is in: Box 22, Folder 13 Part 2 is in: Box 21, Folder 1
    - Skin Annotated Draft (1 of 2), 14 Aug. 2002; 193883 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Skin Annotated Draft (2 of 2), 14 Aug. 2002; 193882 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Skin coverpage "edited, gone through, and input"; Folder "looms, edited, not imput", Undated; 193881 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Series XII: Essay and Story Collections, 193791
  Series XII: Essay and Story Collections contains materials pertaining to Lynne Tillman's several short story works. These materials consist of research, annotated drafts, reviews, etc. This series is divided into four subseries:
  A: Absence Makes the Heart
  B: Madame Realism Complex
  C: The Broad Picture
  D: This Is Not It
  - Series XII, Subseries A: Absence Makes the Heart (1991), 193838
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated; 193878 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated; 193877 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated; 193876 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Absence Makes the Heart, Undated; 193875 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Annotated Draft, Undated; 193874 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Absence Makes the Heart - Annotated Draft, Undated; 193873 (Box 22, Folder 36)